RADHIKA LELE

Front End Web Developer

📞 514-623-9797 💮 radhika.khaparde@gmail.com 📝 www.linkedin.com/in/radhika-lele 📝 https://www.radhikalele.com

SUMMARY

A Front End Developer with a passion for creating responsive and accessible web applications using JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, SASS and Firebase. With a strong foundation in programming, backed by two years of experience in customer service and teaching, I possess a unique blend of technical expertise and interpersonal skills. I am committed to creating engaging and userfriendly experiences for website visitors, and have a keen eye for design and user experience.

PROJECTS

Robo Trivia

robo-trivia-app.netlify.app

https://github.com/RoboTriviaProject/RoboTrivia

Robo Trivia quiz app should let you play a quiz by selecting categories, difficulty level by using open Trivia API.

Recipe Finder App

cool-tiramisu-c44ed3.netlify.app

https://github.com/Radhika-Lele/RadhikaLeleProject3

Recipe Search API allows you to search through millions of web recipes. With the Edamam API, users can search for recipes based on various criteria such as ingredients, diet restrictions, and cuisine types.

NOVAS Boutique Shop

https://peppy-gecko-8d9ad2.netlify.app

https://github.com/Radhika-

Lele/DhaliwalHuangLeleProjectTwo/tree/displayCartNew

Multipage E-commerce website for shopping furniture using HTML5,CSS, SASS, JavaScript and Firebase

Multi-page Site

https://glittering-lily-61b3f1.netlify.app

https://github.com/Radhika-Lele/RadhikaLeleProjectOne

Translated static design images into functional, responsive website using HTML, CSS and SASS

EDUCATION

Web Development Immersive Bootcamp Certificate

Juno College of Technology, Toronto, ON

= 03/2023 - 06/2023

Master of Engineering in Electronics and Telecommunication Engineering

University of Mumbai, India

m 08/2015 - 10/2017

Bachelor of Engineering in Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Amravati University,India

= 08/2010 - 06/2014

SKILLS

HTML	CSS	JavaSc	ript	React
SASS	Git & Git-Hub		Web Accessibility	
Restful APIs		Firebase	Responsive Design	

EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Representative

CURO Financial Technologies

- Resolved customer complaints and inquiries with a 95% satisfaction rating, leading to increased customer retention and loyalty
- Developed strong relationship with customers, resulting in an 89% customer retention rate using modern negotiation tactics
- Managed an average of 50+ customer inquires per day, ensuring all issues were resolved in a timely and satisfactory manner

Customer Service Sales Representative

Alorica

m 05/2019 - 08/2020

- Montreal, Quebec
- Contacted potential customers to capitalize on new sale, cross-sale and up-sale opportunities
- Consistently exceeded sales targets by 80%, building strong relationships with clients, and effectively communicating the value of our products and services

Teaching Assistant

Thakur College of Engineering and Technology (TCET)

m 07/2016 - 06/2017

Mumbai.India

- Taught labs and conducted workshops for 120 undergraduate and graduate students of the **Electronics Engineering division**
- Designed and delivered engaging presentations that have helped students understand complex engineering concepts in a clear and concise manner

CX7 Enhancy